<?xml version="1.0"?>
<data>
	<machine name="Arcade" type="Arcade" release_date="1972">
		<description>
			<text><![CDATA[An arcade game (or coin-op) is a coin-operated entertainment machine, usually installed in public businesses, such as restaurants, bars, and particularly amusement arcades. Most arcade games are video games, pinball machines, electro-mechanical games, redemption games, and merchandisers.
			]]></text>
			<source_url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arcade_game</source_url>
		</description>
		<emulator name="Mame">
			<description>
				<text><![CDATA[
				MAME (an acronym of Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is an emulator application designed to recreate the hardware of arcade game systems in software on modern personal computers and other platforms.
				]]></text>
				<source_url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MAME</source_url>
			</description>
			<platform name="Windows">
				<source_url start_with = "downloader.php?file=releases/mame" end_with = ".exe">http://www.mamedev.org/release.html</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="OS X">
				<source_url>http://sourceforge.net/projects/mameosx/files/latest/download</source_url>
			</platform>
		</emulator>

		<emulator name="Supermodel3">
			<description>
				<text><![CDATA[
				Supermodel emulates Sega Model 3 arcade platform, allowing you to play a number of ground-breaking arcade classics. It uses OpenGL and the SDL library, and can run on Windows, Linux, and Mac OS X.
				]]></text>
				<source_url>http://www.supermodel3.com/</source_url>
			</description>
			<platform name="Windows64">
				<source_url start_with = "Supermodel_" end_with = "Win64.zip">http://www.supermodel3.com/Download.html</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="Windows32">
				<source_url start_with = "Supermodel_" end_with = "Win32.zip">http://www.supermodel3.com/Download.html</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="OS X">
				<source_url start_with = "Supermodel_" end_with = "OSX.tgz">http://www.supermodel3.com/Download.html</source_url>
			</platform>
		</emulator>

		<emulator name="Raine">
			<description>
				<text><![CDATA[
				Raine is an emulator, it emulates some M68000 and M68020 arcade games and is mainly focused on Taito and Jaleco games hardware. It if started as an experiment with the Rainbow Islands
romset, it is now able to emulate many nice games, including new additions from Cave and other companies.
				]]></text>
				<source_url>http://rainemu.swishparty.co.uk/</source_url>
			</description>
			<platform name="Windows">
				<source_url>http://rainemu.swishparty.co.uk/html/download/latest.html</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="OS X">
				<source_url>http://rainemu.swishparty.co.uk/html/download/macos.html</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="Linux">
				<source_url>http://rainemu.swishparty.co.uk/html/archive/debian/</source_url>
			</platform>
		</emulator>
		
		<emulator name="FB Alpha">
			<description>
				<text><![CDATA[
				FB Alpha (formerly FinalBurn Alpha) is a multi-arcade emulator. It emulated various systems from the Capcom CPS-1 to the Toaplan machines and the Neo Geo as well.
				]]></text>
				<source_url>http://www.barryharris.me.uk/fba.php</source_url>
			</description>
			<platform name="Windows">
				<source_url start_with = "fba_" end_with = ".7z">http://www.barryharris.me.uk/fba.php</source_url>
			</platform>
			<platform name="WindowsXP">
				<source_url start_with = "fbaxp_" end_with = ".7z">http://www.barryharris.me.uk/fba.php</source_url>
			</platform>
		</emulator>

		<emulator name="AAE">
			<description>
				<text><![CDATA[
				Another Arcade Emulator is a primarily vector based arcade system emulator written using C and OpenGL. It strives to recreate the experience of playing the games as they were in the arcade, and requires the original game ROMS in order to run. In some cases copies of the original sound files and artwork are required to complete the emulation experience. It provides for simulation options that are not available in MAME, and offers several features that are not available in MAME due to their arcade preservation charter, such as advanced hardware based drawing and motion blur.
				]]></text>
				<source_url>http://pages.suddenlink.net/aae/</source_url>
			</description>
			<platform name="Windows">
				<source_url start_with="aae0" end_with=".zip">http://pages.suddenlink.net/aae/</source_url>
			</platform>
		</emulator>

	</machine>
</data>